"How does a quantum computer
factor large numbers?"
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
- PMS?
- Shor's algorithm.
GABLEHAUSER:
Correct.
Four-point-one-eight-five-five times 10
to the seventh ergs per calorie.
Prévost's theory of exchanges.
Lambda equals one over pi-R-squared N.
Seven hundred and sixty degrees Celsius.
(Howard:)The approximate temperature
of the young lady in the front row.
(Gablehouser:)Mr. Wolowitz,
this is your second warning.
(Sheldon:)A sigma particle.
(Leslie:)Yes, assuming the hypothetical planet
has a mass greater than the Earth.
GABLEHAUSER:
Correct.
(Gablehouser:)Ladies and gentlemen,
I hold in my hand the final question.
(Gablehouser:)The score now stands,
AA, 1150, PMS, 1175.
So for 100 points and the match...